> > Brian Holt: 现在我们有了一个捆束器，我们可以为所欲为，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now we have a bundler,
we can do whatever we want, right?
现在我们有更多的余地去做事情。
Now we have more leeway to do things.
所以我想做的第一件事就是我想把宠物和
So the first thing I want to do
here is I want to split pet and
应用到两个不同的文件对吧
app into two different files, right?
我不知道为什么您没有一个组件，一个文件。
I can't think of a reason why you would
not have one component, one file.
一直都是这样
It's always that way.
文件中没有两个组件。
You don't ever have two
components in a file.
我以前没见过这么好的理由
I've not really seen a good
reason to do that before.
一个组件一个文件
So one component, one file.
所以我要给你们看一个很酷的把戏 VS Code 可以为你做。
So I'm gonna show you a pretty cool
trick that VS Code can do for you.
所以我要强调这一点，然后我把这个小灯泡弄过来。
So I'm gonna highlight this and
then I get this little light bulb here.
该灯泡称为代码操作。
This light bulb is called a code action.
所以我要点击这里，这里还有一些东西。
So I'm gonna click that and
there's a couple things here.
我想要的就是移动
The one that I want is move,
您可能看不到所有这些，因为我安装了其他扩展。
you might not see all of these because
I have other extensions installed.
但你想做的就是搬到一个新的档案里
But the one that you wanna
do is move to a new file,
都是你应该看到的对吧
which all of you should see, right?
因此，单击移动到新文件。
So click move to a new file.
突然我有一个新的 Pet.js 文件
And all the sudden I
have a new Pet.js file
其中有导出，应用程序正在从该文件导入。
which has an export in it, and
app is importing from that file.
挺酷的对吧你喜欢这样吗
It's pretty cool, right,
you like this, cool?
好的
Okay, cool.
所以最酷的是
So what's really cool about it is,
其实是 TypeScript 给你做的
it's actually TypeScript
that does that for you.
这不是 VS .
It's not VS Code.
TypeScript 实际上正在您的代码上运行
TypeScript is actually
running on your code,
虽然我们现在不是在写任何类型的剧本
even though we're not writing
any TypeScript right now.
VS 代码始终在针对您的代码运行 TypeScript ，
VS Code is constantly running
TypeScript against your code,
来理解你的密码是如何运作的
to understand how your code works.
这才是真正能做到的。
And so
that's what's actually able to do that.
现在我更喜欢默认的出口
Now, I prefer default exports, so
我要改变这个来把那些花在花括号里的花去掉
I'm gonna change this to get rid of
those curly braces, and save that.
然后在这里而不是说
And then here, instead of saying,
出口商品 = blah，我想说
export const Pet = blah, I'm gonna say
导出缺省函数 blah .
export default function blah like that.
让我们给这个名字吧
And let's give this a name like so.
>> Brian Holt: 我为什么要这样做 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now why do I do that?
这只是我的默认输出模式
It's just kind of a pattern that
I had that the default export for
组件始终是组件。
components is always the component.
我想说这是个很普通的模式
I would say it's a decently
common pattern, but
我要让你自己来判断
I'll leave you to judge it for yourself.
>> Brian Holt: 在将其更改为指定组件方面，这对于
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: As far as changing it to
a named component, this is useful for
当你在调试东西的时候
when you're debugging things.
因为如果有堆积痕迹
Because if there's a stack trace,
你会看到宠物有这个错误，这使得以后更容易调试。
you'll see pet has the error, which makes
that a little bit easier to debug later.
现在，我们有两个不同的文件，对吗 ?
So now,
we have two different files, right?
我们从宠物进口宠物
We're importing pet from pet.
这仍应以应有的方式进行。
This should still work the way it should.
确实有
It does.
但现在他们的组织结构变得更好了
But now they're a little bit better
organized now that we have an app
组件和
component and
一个宠物组件，它们在不同的文件中，我们可以分开保存它们。
a pet component, and they're in separate
files and we can maintain them separately.
这里还有一个承诺如果你落后了你就可以
There's another commit point here, that if
you've fallen behind, you can go ahead and
我觉得这个承诺
come up to I think this commit.
让我们看看它叫什么
Let's just take a look and
see what it's called.
就在那儿
It's right there.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，这是添加 Parcel，构建过程和抽取 Pet
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this one is the add
Parcel, build process and extract out Pet
这就是你现在想做的一件
components so this is the one that
you'd want to move up to right now.
好吧我们用了包裹
Okay and so we used Parcel.
我告诉过你可以用 Webpack 做 100% 的工作
I told you could use Webpack this
would 100% work with Webpack as well.
您还可以使用 Browserify，这是另一个用于捆绑代码的伟大项目。
You could also use Browserify, which is
another great project for bundling code.
虽然别人会说，但仍然运作良好。
It still works really well despite
what other people might say.
年纪大一点，但还是很不错的。
It's a bit older, but
it still works great.
也可以使用 Rollup 。
Or you could use Rollup as well.
上卷有点不方便有时更难使用
Roll up is a bit more unwieldy
sometimes a little bit harder to use,
但工作也很顺利
but works well, as well.
现在我们介绍了一个 package.json ，
At this point,
now we've introduced a package.json so
如果你在这个过程中向前推进的话
if you're moving forward and
commit points in the course, make sure you
在落实中向前移动，然后在以后运行 npm 安装，对吗 ?
move forward in the commit, and then
you run npm install afterwards, right?
所以，如果我来到这里，不是这个，这个。
So if I come to my terminal here,
not this one, this one.
我说如果我在承诺中向前迈进
And I say,
if I moved forward in the commit,
我得说， npm install，就像这样。
I would have to say,
npm install, just like that.
然后把所有东西都从 npm 的注册表中跑出来
And it's gonna go run and install
everything off of the npm registry.
如果你一直在跟踪你就不用这么做了
You don't have to do this if you've been
following along, but just so you know,
确保您始终与 npm 安装保持一致。
make sure that you're always keeping
up with the npm installs as well.
否则事情就不起作用了
Otherwise, things won't work.